

CONTACT

- info@resumekraft.com
- 202-555-0120
- O Chicago, Illinois, US
- in linkedin.com/resumekraft

SKILLS

PHP

MySQL

Java Script

HTML5

CSS3

Responsive Design

Java

EDUCATION

Finance, Accounting and Insurances; Master's Degree

San Jose State University 2014 - 2018 Finance, Accounting and Insurances

Finance and Accounting Northeastern University 2011 - 2013 Bachelor of Finance and Accounting

SUMMARY

I have decided to change my career to programming. I have always been interested in programming and last year I attended a programming course. During course I learnt about basics of PHP, HTML, CSS, XML, MySQL, object-oriented programming, Javascript.

Moreover since then I developed my skills. My goal is to improve my knowledge and gain experience in programming.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Compliance Analyst/Compliance Analyst MoneyGram International Apr 2017 - Sep 2019

- Evaluating fraudulent or suspicious activity of transactions
- Managing the investigative process from initial detection to disposition
- Reporting to Goverments Regulators considering guidelines and country regulatory requirements
- Training of new joiners

KYC/AML Analyst for Deutsche Bank

HCL Technologies 2016 - 2016

- Undertaking quality reviews of clients' KYC records
- Investigating and escalating issues related with client types and structures, financial products and services
- Verifying client data in line with regulatory requirements
- Classifying clients risk level from regulatory perspective

AML Analyst

Citibank International Limited 2014 - 2016

- Analysing alerts and investigating transactional activities to detect any suspicions of money laundering and terrorist financing activity
- Operating with agreed business SLAs and confidentiality standards
- Analysing data derived from internal systems and the Internet
- Building and applying knowledge of money laundering process

LANGUAGES